<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<LanguageData>

    <!-- Ransom demand -->
    <MFI_ExtortionDemandTitle>extortion demand at {0}</MFI_ExtortionDemandTitle>
    <MFI_ExtortionDemand>{0}, {1} of {2}, contacts you on the Comms Console. Based on your proximity to their {3} {4}, HE feels you are encroaching on their terrain.\n\nHECAP says HE is willing to overlook this transgression for a modest fee of {5} silver. HECAP adds that failure to pay will be met with aggression, but HE is gracefully willing to give you a day to pay.</MFI_ExtortionDemand>
    
    <!-- Reverse Trade Request -->
    <MFI_ReverseTradeRequest_Pyro>{0}, {1} of {2}, has sent us a message. Their nearby settlement {3} had an incident with a pyromaniac and are now desperate for {4}. They are willing to pay extra for any items of this category, but will need {5} silver to cover costs for the caravan.\n\n{0} assures us the offending pyromaniac will stay home.</MFI_ReverseTradeRequest_Pyro>
    <MFI_ReverseTradeRequest_Mechs>A somewhat rushed and poorly written message from {0}, {1} of {2}, reached us. Their nearby settlement {3} narrowly escaped a deadly encounter with mechanoids! They've started to rebuild, but they would like our help. Specifically, they are desperate for {4}. They are willing to pay extra for any items of this category, but will need {5} silver to hire a caravan as their settlement can't spare the manpower.</MFI_ReverseTradeRequest_Mechs>
    <MFI_ReverseTradeRequest_Caravan>We have received a humble request from {0}, {1} of {2}. Their nearby settlement of {3} has mismanaged their time and is now desperate for {4}. They are willing to pay extra for any items of this category, but will need {5} silver to cover costs for the caravan.</MFI_ReverseTradeRequest_Caravan>
    <MFI_ReverseTradeRequest_Pirates>{0}, {1} of {2}, has sent us a message. Their nearby settlement {3} was recently ravaged by pirates and are now desperate for {4}. They are willing to pay extra for any items of this category, but will need {5} silver to cover costs for the caravan.</MFI_ReverseTradeRequest_Pirates>
    <MFI_ReverseTradeRequest_Hardship>An anonymous broker contacts you on the Comms Console. He has been in contact with {2} and has managed to strike a deal for {4}. He has managed to negotiate for a trader to pay extra for any items of this category, but he requests {5} silver as a brokerage fee before he'll send the caravan.</MFI_ReverseTradeRequest_Hardship>
    <MFI_ReverseTradeRequest_Blight>{0} sends us a message on behalf of the nearby settlement of {3}. Their crops have been struck by blight and they might not survive the winter without extra supplies of {4}. They are willing to pay extra for any items of this category, but without immediate food or money they will starve. They need at least {5} silver to tide them.</MFI_ReverseTradeRequest_Blight>
    <MFI_ReverseTradeRequestTitle>trading opportunity at {0}</MFI_ReverseTradeRequestTitle>

    <MFI_LetterLabel_HarvestRequest>Help wanted</MFI_LetterLabel_HarvestRequest>
    <MFI_LetterHarvestRequest>A nearby settlement, {0}, contacts you with a special request. Their fields have yielded far more than originally expected, and they could really use your help with the harvest.\n\nThis request expires after: {1}\n\nIf you want to help them, send a caravan with capable growers. You can review this offer by selecting {0} on the world map.</MFI_LetterHarvestRequest>
    <MFI_CommandFulfillBumperCropHarvestConfirm>Offer your help in harvesting? {0} will spend some time here.</MFI_CommandFulfillBumperCropHarvestConfirm>
    <MFI_MessageBumperCropNoGrower>No conscious, capable grower.</MFI_MessageBumperCropNoGrower>

</LanguageData>