<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Defs>

    <MoreFactionInteraction.EventDef>
        <defName>MFI_GameOfUrComp</defName>
        <theme>the Royal Game-of-Ur</theme>
        <themeDesc>Send your best gamer.</themeDesc>
        <learnedSkills>
            <li>Intellectual</li>
            <li>Social</li>
        </learnedSkills>
        <relevantStat>PsychicSensitivity</relevantStat>
        <workerClass>MoreFactionInteraction.EventRewardWorker_GameOfUrComp</workerClass>
        <xPGainFirstOther>0</xPGainFirstOther>
        <outComeFirstPlace>Through skill, nerves of steel and a good amount of luck, [PAWN_nameDef] won the tournament! Your reward for participating is:\n\n{0}</outComeFirstPlace>
        <outcomeFirstLoser>For the tense final round, [PAWN_nameDef] went head to head with the five-year reigning champion and lost. Your reward for participating is:\n\n{0}</outcomeFirstLoser>
        <outComeFirstOther>During the second inning of the fifth round, [PAWN_nameDef] played a move which confused [PAWN_possessive] opponent and astounded referees. Understandably, a massive brawl ensued. Your reward for participating is:\n\n{0}</outComeFirstOther>
        <rewardFirstPlace>Reward_gameOfUrCompFirstPlace</rewardFirstPlace>
        <rewardFirstLoser>Reward_gameOfUrCompFirstLoser</rewardFirstLoser>
        <rewardFirstOther>Reward_gameOfUrCompFirstOther</rewardFirstOther>
    </MoreFactionInteraction.EventDef>

    <MoreFactionInteraction.EventDef>
        <defName>MFI_ShootingComp</defName>
        <theme>a shooting competition</theme>
        <themeDesc>Send your best shot.</themeDesc>
        <learnedSkills>
            <li>Shooting</li>
        </learnedSkills>
        <relevantStat>ShootingAccuracyPawn</relevantStat>
        <workerClass>MoreFactionInteraction.EventRewardWorker_ShootingComp</workerClass>
        <outComeFirstPlace>With almost robotic accuracy, [PAWN_nameDef] took aim and hit all targets with pinpoint precision. Judges were very impressed and rewarded you with:\n\n{0}</outComeFirstPlace>
        <outcomeFirstLoser>There was a strong field of contenders this year, with many faction representatives having lived as a hunter or just plain decked out in (archotech) bionics. [PAWN_nameDef] stranded somewhere in the quarter finals. Your reward for participating is:\n\n{0}</outcomeFirstLoser>
        <outComeFirstOther>[PAWN_nameDef] did not proceed past the first round, which consisted of "hit the broad side of a barn". They added that part as a gag years ago. [PAWN_nameDef] is the first since its introduction not to progress to the second round. Your reward for participating is:\n\n{0}</outComeFirstOther>
        <rewardFirstPlace>Reward_shootingCompFirstPlace</rewardFirstPlace>
        <rewardFirstLoser>Reward_shootingCompFirstLoser</rewardFirstLoser>
        <rewardFirstOther>Reward_shootingCompFirstOther</rewardFirstOther>
    </MoreFactionInteraction.EventDef>

    <MoreFactionInteraction.EventDef>
        <defName>MFI_CulturalSwap</defName>
        <theme>culture and art</theme>
        <themeDesc>There may be an opportunity for trade.</themeDesc>
        <learnedSkills>
            <li>Social</li>
            <li>Social</li>
            <li>Artistic</li>
        </learnedSkills>
        <relevantStat>SocialImpact</relevantStat>
        <workerClass>MoreFactionInteraction.EventRewardWorker_CulturalSwap</workerClass>
        <!-- {0 = childhood backstory label} -->
        <outComeFirstPlace>As the last of daylight slowly dimmed away, [PAWN_nameDef] simply sat down on a granite stool and told of [PAWN_objective] upbringing as a [PAWN_title]. This simple story and more importantly the atmosphere [PAWN_objective] created was lauded by judges for its intimacy, originality and bravery. Your reward for participating is:\n\n{0}</outComeFirstPlace>
        <outcomeFirstLoser>Not being better prepared or having brought anything, your caravan broke out in a song and dance routine with [PAWN_nameDef] taking centre stage. It wasn't well-rehearsed, which shone through the performance. Not all participating factions were able to appreciate the improvised show, but it was an admirable effort nonetheless. Your reward for participating is:\n\n{0}</outcomeFirstLoser>
        <outComeFirstOther>The host faction moved the audience to tears with their dazzling display; a dramatic reenactment of their ancestor's discovery of White Rabbit Mountain Range. It was a touching piece of theatre that transcended language barriers, and reached the hearts of young and old alike.\n\nAnd then there was your troupe. Your reward for participating is:\n\n{0}</outComeFirstOther>
        <rewardFirstPlace>Reward_culturalSwapFirstPlace</rewardFirstPlace>
        <rewardFirstLoser>Reward_culturalSwapFirstLoser</rewardFirstLoser>
        <rewardFirstOther>Reward_culturalSwapFirstOther</rewardFirstOther>
    </MoreFactionInteraction.EventDef>

    <MoreFactionInteraction.EventDef>
        <defName>MFI_ScienceFaire</defName>
        <theme>exchanging scientific discoveries</theme>
        <themeDesc>Exciting!</themeDesc>
        <learnedSkills>
            <li>Intellectual</li>
        </learnedSkills>
        <relevantStat>ResearchSpeed</relevantStat>
        <workerClass>MoreFactionInteraction.EventRewardWorker_ScienceFaire</workerClass>
        <outComeFirstPlace>Settling in easily, a powerful orator and great scholar explains you nothing about the complexities of the universe. Instead they reveal its simplicities:\n\n{0}</outComeFirstPlace>
        <outcomeFirstLoser>Your caravan nestles in between members of a group called "appreciators of science". They bestow upon you a gift of knowledge:\n\n{0}</outcomeFirstLoser>
        <outComeFirstOther>Weary from the long journey, your caravan members have trouble staying awake during the long and tenuous lecture by a famous professor. As a departure gift, you get:\n\n{0}</outComeFirstOther>
        <rewardFirstPlace>Reward_scienceFaireFirstPlace</rewardFirstPlace>
        <rewardFirstLoser>Reward_scienceFaireFirstLoser</rewardFirstLoser>
        <rewardFirstOther>Reward_scienceFaireFirstOther</rewardFirstOther>
    </MoreFactionInteraction.EventDef>

    <MoreFactionInteraction.EventDef>
        <defName>MFI_AcousticShow</defName>
        <theme>an acoustic show</theme>
        <themeDesc>You wonder whether to bring earplugs.</themeDesc>
        <learnedSkills>
            <li>Artistic</li>
        </learnedSkills>
        <relevantStat>TradePriceImprovement</relevantStat>
        <workerClass>MoreFactionInteraction.EventRewardWorker_AcousticShow</workerClass>
        <outComeFirstPlace>Your caravan spent the day gallivanting through the stalls and admiring the wide array of eclectic non-electric musical instruments from all over this world and beyond. As dusk fell and people gathered their instruments an intimate concert was held on the main-stage. It lifted the spirits of your caravan members. Your reward for coming is:\n\n{0}</outComeFirstPlace>
        <outcomeFirstLoser>The expo turned out to be a very cosy get-together, spent jamming on guitars. Someone played Wonderwall but other than that it was a pretty chill evening that put everybody in a good mood. Your reward for coming is:\n\n{0}</outcomeFirstLoser>
        <outComeFirstOther>One of your caravan members picked up an instrument they shouldn't have and, not being musically gifted, broke a string while fingering a minor. Apologies were made but it wasn't sufficient: your klutzy caravan member was to work as a stage-hand on the night of the performance. Since a good time was still had by all, they were given the after-party leftovers:\n\n{0}</outComeFirstOther>
        <rewardFirstPlace>Reward_acousticShowFirstPlace</rewardFirstPlace>
        <rewardFirstLoser>Reward_acousticShowFirstLoser</rewardFirstLoser>
        <rewardFirstOther>Reward_acousticShowFirstOther</rewardFirstOther>
    </MoreFactionInteraction.EventDef>

</Defs>